<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Nicholas Matragkas</title>
    <link>nmatra.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Nicholas Matragkas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Nicholas Matragkas</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="nmatra.github.io/project/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>MADES</title>
      <link>nmatra.github.io/project/mades/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nmatra.github.io/project/mades/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The MADES project was a Specific Targeted Research Project (STREP) of the Seventh Framework Programme for research and technological development (FP7). MADES aimed to develop a holistic, model-driven approach to improve the practice in the development of embedded systems. The proposed approach covered all phases, from design to code generation and deployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Design activities in MADES exploited a dedicated language developed as an extension to OMG&amp;rsquo;s MARTE Profile. Validation activities played a key role in the context of MADES and they included the verification of key properties on designed artefacts, closed-loop simulation based on detailed models of the environment, and the verification of designed transformations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Code generation addressed both hardware description languages and conventional programming languages with features for compile-time virtualisation of common hardware architecture features, including accelerators, memory, multiprocessor and inter-processor communication channels, to cope with the fact that hardware platforms are getting more and more complex.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MONDO</title>
      <link>nmatra.github.io/project/mondo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nmatra.github.io/project/mondo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As Model Driven Engineering (MDE) is increasingly applied to larger and more complex systems, the current generation of modelling and model management technologies are being pushed to their limits in terms of capacity and efficiency, and as such, additional research is imperative in order to enable MDE to remain relevant with industrial practice and continue delivering its widely recognised productivity, quality, and maintainability benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of the MONDO project is to tackle the increasingly important challenge of scalability in MDE in a comprehensive manner. Achieving scalability in modelling and MDE involves being able to construct large models and domain specific languages in a systematic manner, enabling teams of modellers to construct and refine large models in a collaborative manner, advancing the state-of-the-art in model querying and transformations tools so that they can cope with large models (of the scale of millions of model elements), and providing an infrastructure for efficient storage, indexing and retrieval of large models.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSSMETER</title>
      <link>nmatra.github.io/project/ossmeter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nmatra.github.io/project/ossmeter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The aim of the OSSMETER project was to extend the state-of-the-art in the field of automated analysis and measurement of open-source software (OSS), and to develop a platform that will support decision makers in the process of discovering, comparing, assessing and monitoring the health, quality, impact and activity of open-source software. To this end, software tools were developed which supported the computation of trustworthy quality indicators by performing advanced analysis and integration of information from diverse sources including the project metadata, source code repositories, communication channels and bug tracking systems of OSS projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OSSMETER was not another OSS forge but instead it provided a meta-platform for analysing existing OSS projects that are developed in existing OSS forges and foundations such as SourceForge, Google Code, GitHub, Eclipse, Mozilla and Apache.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
